{
    "subject": "resource/I'm_No_Dummy",
    "predicate": "ontology/abstract",
    "object": "I'm No Dummy is a 2009 documentary film about ventriloquism directed by Bryan W. Simon, produced by Marjorie Engesser through Montivagus Productions.  It premiered at the 2009 Seattle International Film Festival before being released theatrically in the United States by Salient Media and NBCUniversal in 2010.The comic documentary examines and deconstructs this now obscure art form through clips, photos and interviews with many of the greatest \u201cvents\u201d from today and yesterday as well as their puppets. The idea came to Simon while on a bike ride in Los Angeles, as he kicked around ideas for a new project and decided to focus on a documentary about something he loved as a child. The film stars Jeff Dunham, Jay Johnson and Lynn Trefzger and features Kelly Asbury, Tom Ladshaw, Jimmy Nelson and Willie Tyler.  Archival footage of Edgar Bergen, Paul Winchell and Senor Wences is also included in the feature.",
    "human_readable": "The abstract of I'M No Dummy is a 2009 documentary film about ventriloquism directed by Bryan W. Simon, produced by Marjorie Engesser through Montivagus Productions.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9161273241043091,
            "question": "Who directed the documentary film 'I'M No Dummy'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.907493531703949,
            "question": "Who produced the documentary 'I'M No Dummy'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8632757663726807,
            "question": "What is the subject of the documentary 'I'M No Dummy'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8169935345649719,
            "question": "What year was the documentary 'I'M No Dummy' released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7772435545921326,
            "question": "What type of film is 'I'M No Dummy'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6892328262329102,
            "question": "What are some common themes explored in documentaries about ventriloquism?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6656351685523987,
            "question": "What is the name of the production company behind 'I'M No Dummy'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6002411842346191,
            "question": "Is 'I'M No Dummy' a fictional or non-fiction film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5629371404647827,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about the production company behind 'I'M No Dummy'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.13294103741645813,
            "question": "Are there any other famous documentaries about performing arts?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The abstract of I'M No Dummy is a 2009 documentary film about ventriloquism directed by Bryan W. Simon, produced by Marjorie Engesser through Montivagus Productions.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5750_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about the production company behind 'I'M No Dummy'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5750_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is 'I'M No Dummy' a fictional or non-fiction film?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5750_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the production company behind 'I'M No Dummy'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5750_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5750_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5750_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5750_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5750_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5750_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5750_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5750_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5750_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5750_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5750_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the provided context information and without prior knowledge, here's the evaluation of the query:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents confirm that I'M No Dummy is a documentary film about ventriloquism, directed by Bryan W. Simon, and produced by Marjorie Engesser through Montivagus Productions."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation:\n- The information provided in the documents describes a documentary titled \"I'm No Dummy\" directed by Bryan W. Simon and produced by Marjorie Engesser through their production company, Montivagus Productions.\n- The document also states that the film is about ventriloquism and was completed within a year.\n- It mentions interviews with notable ventriloquist performers such as Jay Johnson, Jeff Dunham, and Lynn Trefzger.\n- Therefore, the abstract provided for \"I'm No Dummy\" aligns well with the details given in the documents."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}